Guide to the COLLECTION NAME HERE, YYYY-YYYY IBT0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Campaigns, Educational videos, Promotions, Rallies, Safety videos and Other Miscellaneous Videos, Series 3
  - Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America, 1993; Series 3; VHS (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America, 1993; Series 3; VHS (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - A Road Map to Skills for Tomorrow: A Young Persons Guide to Union Careers, Series 3; VHS (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - RTA Union Organizing, Series 3; VHS (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Safe Winter Truck Driving, Series 3; VHS (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Safe Winter Truck Driving, Series 3; VHS (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Saipan Clothing Manufacturers- Edited Version and Follow-Up ABC-TV 20/20, 1998-03-13; 1998-03-20; Series 3; VHS (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Saipan Sweatshop (AND) Introduction to AFL-CIO Union- Industries Show, Series 3; VHS (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Scepter of Violence (History), Series 3; U-Matic (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - "Sending Them a Message: Teamsters Take on the Special Interests" 12:25, 1993-05; Series 3; VHS (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - The Sexual Harassment Quiz, Series 3; VHS (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Sinclair Broadcasting WGME News 13 at 11:00 (Portland), 2004-10-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - "Sinclair Broadcasting" CBS New Portland, 2004-10-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Something to Hide National Labor Committee, 1999; Series 3; VHS (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Special Events Report IBT "Union and Ex-Conflicts" by Rev. C. Dismas Clark, Series 3; Audio cassette (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - A Speech to Teamsters Local 710 Members Chicago, Illinois, 1994-09-25; Series 3; Audio Casstte (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Stand for Children- America Needs a Raise Pre-activities #1, 1996-06-1; Series 3; Betacam (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Stand for Children- America Needs a Raise Teamsters March, Pre-activities #2, 1996-06-01; Series 3; Betacam (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Stand for Children #3, 1996-06-01; Series 3; Betacam (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Standing Up for American Jobs: The Detroit Newspaper Strike, 1995-11-14; Series 3; VHS (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - State of DC Schools Prime Time Report, 2005-10-25; Series 3; VHS (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - State of DC Schools Prime Time Report, 2005-10-25; Series 3; VHS (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - "Stay Alert... For Life!" Fatigue and Alertness and the Commercial Truck Driver- The Driver Fatigue and Alertness Study, Series 3; VHS (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Sterling Heights, MI Police Attack Striking Detroit News/Free Press Workers, 1995; Series 3; VHS (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Strengthen Social Security, Series 3; VHS (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - "Strike-Out???" IBT Drive, 1991-04-24; Series 3; VHS (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters "A Long Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future", 2003-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters "A Long Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future", 2003-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters "A Long Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future" RT 10:03 Mono Mix, 2003-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters "A Long Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future" RT 10:03 Mono Mix, 2003-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters "A Long Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future" RT 10:03, 2003-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters "A Long Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future" RT 46:52 Mono Mix, 2003-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - A Strong Legacy, A powerful Future 1 of 6, 2004-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - A Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future Tape 2 of 6, 2004-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - A Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future Tape 3 of 6, 2004-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - A Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future Tape 4 of 6, 2004-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - A Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future Tape 5 of 6, 2004-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - A Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future Tape 6 of 6, 2004-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - A Strong Legacy- A powerful Future, 2004-09-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - "A Strong Union Involves Everyone", 1995; Series 3; VHS (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Teamster #4 Cartridge, Series 3; AMpex 406 Mastering Audio Tape (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Teamster's/America West "Speak Out", 2004; Series 3; VHS (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Teamster Canada Growing Together, Series 3; VHS (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Teamster Canada Growing Together, Series 3; VHS (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters- Casino Rama Rally with James Hoffa Tape 2, Series 3; Ampex 406 mastering audio tape (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters: "A Changing Union in a Changing World", Series 3; VHS (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Endorsement of Clinton IBT, CBS Evening News, Washington DC, 1992-07-15; Series 3; VHS (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters to Support Clinton News Segments, 1992-10-13; Series 3; Betacam (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Teamster December 10th, Series 3; Ampex 406 mastering audio tape (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Dedication Ribbon Cutting, Series 3; VHS (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Dinner International Inn, 1964-06-09; Series 3; mastering audio tape (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Dinner International Inn, 1964-06-09; Series 3; mastering audio tape (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Disaffiliation from the AFL-CIO, Inside Politics with Candy Crowley, Newsnight with Aaron Brown, 2005-07-25; Series 3; VHS (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters Dissaffiliation from the AFL-CIO, 2005-07-25; Series 3; VHS (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Dissaffiliation from the AFL-CIO, 2005-07-05; Series 3; VHS (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters- Driving America's Future, Series 3; VHS (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters: Dignity and Strength, Series 3; VHS (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters: Farmland Dairy Spot Ashley Thomas V.O. DAT Original Recording, 1996-03-11; Series 3; Digital audio tape (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - "Teamster Fat Cats", Series 3; VHS (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Food Relief Portland/Eugene, OR, 1996-03-02; Series 3; VHS (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Flood Relief in Portland KGW TV INBC News, Portland, 1996-03-02; Series 3; VHS (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters "Home of the Brave" Documentary Counterpoint Films Viola Liuzzo, Series 3; VHS (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters and JAB (Joint Association of Boxers) Friday Night Fights ESPN 2, 2004-07-09; Series 3; VHS (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters K-Mart Anti-Union "Bump Up from VHS", 1996-06-20; Series 3; Betacam (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - "Teamsters- Labor Day Federal Elections Get Out the Vote Rally" St. Louis, 1996-09-02; Series 3; VHS (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Leadership Academy for New Local Officers- Teamsters Education Department 3 of 3, 1996; Series 3; Audio cassette (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Labor Day Rally Coney Island Tape 1, 2003-09-01; Series 3; Betacam (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Local 25 "Working for you!" Full Version 11:30, 2000; Series 3; VHS (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Local 25 Charlestown, MA Tape 3 of 3, Series 3; Betacam (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Louisville Overnite- Strike Footage #3 of 5, 2000-03-10; Series 3; Betacam (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Memphis Overnite Tape 1, 1999-09-12; Series 3 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters/Make-a-wish Convoy, 1991; Series 3; VHS (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters and Our Communities: Hand in Hand, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters and Our Communities: Hand in Hand, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters and Our Communities: Hand in Hand 6 min, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Union: "Teamsters and Our Communities: Hand in Hand" -Dubbed Master Copy-, 1996-07-23; Series 3; Betacam (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters and Our Communities: Hand in Hand, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Overnite Rally at Bed, Bath and Beyond -Jimmy Hoffa B-Roll #2, 1999-12-09; Series 3; Betacam (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Picket "Joye Coyle" Production CBS, ABC, NBC; Pittsburgh, Series 3; VHS (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Teamster's/Piedmont Organizing "Mechanic's Voice" IBT Communications-2004, Series 3; VHS (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Protest NBC, Detroit "Destroyed" Copy, 2001-11-10; Series 3; VHS (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Peurto Rico Red Cross Disaster Training, 1996-06; Series 3; VHS (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - The Teamsters "Putting Members First" Generic Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters: Putting the Members First, 1994; Series 3; VHS (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Putting the Members First, Series 3; VHS (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Rally Columbus, OH Tape 1, 2000-10-31; Series 3; Betacam (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Rally Columbus, OH Tape 2, 2000-10-31; Series 3; Betacam (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Rally Columbus, OH Tape 3, 2000-10-31; Series 3; Betacam (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Rally- Congress Get Out the Vote Rally, Cleveland- Channel 3 News, 1996-09-29; Series 3; VHS (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Training Demonstration Project Rancho Murieta, CA, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Hazmat Demonstration Ranch Murieta Training Center Tape 1, Series 3; U-Matic (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Rally for Striking NMH Nurses with Jim Hoffa Petoskey, Michigan, 2003-04-12; Series 3; VHS (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Rock Vegas Rally America West/Clark County Organization Tape 1 of 2, 2002-10-16; Series 3; Betacam (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Rock Vegas Rally0 America West/Clark County Las Vegas, Nevada Tape 2 of 2, 2002-10-16; Series 3; VHS (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Satellite Feeds Protection May 18-21, Series 3; U-Matic (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters in Seattle Against WTO Bump 2 (Undated), Series 3; Betacam (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters, 1976-09-18; Series 3; U-Matic (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Spot Flour Mill Georgetown #1, 1983-06-06; Series 3; U-Matic (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Spot Flour Mill Georgetown #2, 1983-06-06; Series 3; U-Matic (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Strike Overnite Freight, 1999; Series 3; VHS (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters and UPS Contract CBS Evening News, 2002-07-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters and UPS Contract Parcel-UPS 2002 Contract Negotiations CBS Evening News, 2002-07-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters and UPS Contract CBS Evening News, 2002-07-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters and UPS Contract CBS Evening News, 2002-07-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters and UPS Contract CBS Evening News, 2002-07-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters and UPS Contract CBS Evening News, 2002-07-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - The Teamsters v PFAA "Teamsters Local 2000 or PFAA the Decision is Yours', 2003-05-09; Series 3; VHS (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - "Teamster Women on the Move" 6 min, 1994; Series 3; VHS (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - "Teens vs Teamsters" Inside Politics, CNN National, 2004-01-15; Series 3; VHS (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - "There's More Than One Way to Skin a Cat" United Auto Workers, Series 3; VHS (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Time for Unity IBT Time 11:19, Series 3; VHS (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Transportation Information Services Org. Anti-Hoffa 1962/1963, Series 3; Fideli-tape reel to reel (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - "Triple Trailer" ABC News Tonight Special with Peter Jennings McNeil/Lehrer Report, "Triple Trailers/ CRASH", 1991-05-13-1991-05-14; Series 3; VHS (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - "Trouble on the Tracks" Discovery Times Channel Rail Conference, 2004-11-14; Series 3; VHS (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - "Trouble on the Tracks" Discovery Times Channel Rail Conference, 2004-11-14; Series 3; VHS (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Trusteeships + Rico Tape 1, 1989-04-07; Series 3; VHS (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Trusteeships + Rico Tape 2, 1989-04-07; Series 3; VHS (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - "Turn It Around: Teamster Stewards Solving Problems on the Job" 17min, 1994; Series 3; VHS (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - "Turn it Around" Teamsters Stewards Solving Problems on the Job 17 min, Series 3; VHS (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - UFCW Walmart "Not as Advertised" 8min, 1999-11; Series 3; Betacam (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Union Voice, 1995-11-2; Series 3; Audio cassette (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Union Voice, 1995-11-9; Series 3; Audio cassette (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Union Labor Life Insurance- Commercials Produced by the Direct Marketing Department, Series 3; VHS (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - "Unions Today" 30 min, Series 3; VHS (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Unite! Exposing Cintas Trt: 9:04, 2006-06-20; Series 3; Betacam (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - United we win IBT Carhaul Contract Campaign, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - United Farmworkers of America: The Wrath of Grapes -English Version-, Series 3; VHS (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - "United Parcel Service 1987-1990 Proposed Agreement" Parcel + Small Package Trade Division IBT Chauffers, Warehousemen + Helpers of America, Series 3; VHS (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Unity- Teamsters Hour #23-24, 1985-01-27-1985-01-28; Series 3; VHS (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - "UPS Rally" Parcel- UPS 2002 Contract Negotiations Las Vegas UPS Caravan Rally, 2002-05-01; Series 3; VHS (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Unsolved Labor Mysteries: Episode 1 "The Alien Abduction of Ron Carey", Series 3; VHS (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - US Air Begins with US!, 1994; Series 3; VHS and CD (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - "US Airways Rally" ABC 15 News 12 News Today, 2006-02-13; Series 3; VHS (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - USA NAFTA #1 AFL-CIO "Bad Deal" and USA NAFTA #2, 1993-10-08; Series 3; VHS (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Walmart: Not as Advertised IBT 9:30 min, Series 3; VHS (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Wal-mart: Not as Advertised Community Voice Video Productions David White- IBT 9:11min, Series 3; VHS (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Wal-mart Workers: Organizing to Keep Sam Walton's Dream Alive- A Worker VoiceVideo Production, Series 3; VHS (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Warehouse "AWG Teamsters Strike Ends" News 5 at Ten, KCTV-TV Kansas City, 2000-06-02; Series 3; VHS (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - We Do the Work "Leaving Home" Short Version RT 14 min, Series 3; VHS (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - We Do the Work "Leaving Home" Short Version 14 min, Series 3; VHS (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - We Voted "Yes" IBT Organizing Department, 1985; Series 3; VHS (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, Series 3; VHS (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Edited Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Edited Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Edited Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Spanish Edition, Series 3; VHS (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Spanish Edition (Original), Series 3; VHS (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Spanish Edition, Series 3; VHS (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Spanish Edition, Series 3; VHS (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters Spanish Version, 2003-01-23; Series 3; VHS (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - "Welcome to the Teamsters" Spanish-Language Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters RT 13:32, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters RT 13:32, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters RT 13:32, 2001; Series 3; vhs (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters RT 13:32, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters RT 13:32, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; vhs (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; VHS (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, 2001; Series 3; vhs (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - "What You Say Matters" from IBT to John J Perry Secretary Tresurer, Teamsters, 15min, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Whatever it Takes: The 2002 UPS Contract, Series 3; vhs (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Whatever it Takes: The 2002 UPS Contract, Series 3; VHS (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Where Do You Stand? Stories from an American Mill RT 60:40, 2003-11; Series 3; VHS (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Where Do You Stand? Stories from an American Mill RT 60:40, 2003-11; Series 3; VHS (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Where Your Dollars Go, Teamsters, 04-01; Series 3; VHS (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - The Wireless Foundation, Good Morning America- Call to Protect Hilights, 2000-03; Series 3; VHS (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Women and AIDS in America: Hidden Crisis, Series 3; VHS (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Women in the Workplace-M. Thomas Production, 1987-03-03; Series 3; VHS (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - "Women's Legal Rights PSA" Teamsters Union. 30sec, 1994; Series 3; VHS (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - "Women's Legal Rights PSA" Teamsters Union, 1994; Series 3; VHS (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Worker Abuse @ Overnite Trans Comp, IBT International Overnite Compaign, Series 3; Betacam (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - The Working Group WTO Footage, Seattle (preview), 1999-12; Series 3; VHS (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - WTO Music Video (undated), VHS (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - WTO Music Video RT 2:04, Series 3; VHS (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - WTO Music Video RT 2:04, Series 3; VHS (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - WTO Music Video RT 2:04, Series 3; VHS (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - WTO Music Video RT 2:04, Series 3; VHS (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - WTO Music Video RT 2:04, Series 3; VHS (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - WTO Music Video RT 2:04, Series 3; VHS (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - WTO Music Video RT 2:04, Series 3; VHS (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Zoned for Slavery: The Child Behind the Label, National Labor Committee, 1995; Series 3; VHS (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Zoned for Slavery: The Child Behind the Label, National Labor Committee, 1995; Series 3; VHS (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - IBT "Changing Union" fine cut #4, 1997-05-13; Series 3; U-matic (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters-Spanish Version Voice over Tape 2 of 2, 2002-09-17; Series 3; betacam (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - IBT Unity, Organization for Power, 2004; Series 3; Betacam (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Employees Presentation Bally's Mission Statement, Bally's Las Vegas, 1999-04-21; Series 3; Betacam (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - IBT education Final Edit, master copy, 2001-07-20; Series 3; Betacam (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, Spanish Language Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, Spanish Language Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, Spanish Language Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, Spanish Language Version, Series 3; VHS (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Partnership with Habitat for Humanity- Master Copy, 1996-02; Series 3; Betacam (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, Spanish Language Version Tape 1 of 2, 2002-09-17; Series 3; Betacam (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - TKG Exhibit Hall Western Union Ball Roy Herrick Int. Clara Day, 1991-06-23; Series 3; Betacam (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Welcome to the Teamsters, Series 3; Betacam (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - SF #22 Interviews with Nurses Outside Bowling Alley- Hawthorne Cutaways of Nurses Ratification Meeting- End of Questions Testimonials of Comm. Members, 1985-01-27; DVD (Box 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Port Truckers' Rally Tape 1, 2000-03-22; DVD (Box 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Teamsters Rally- Coney Island Tape 1 CINTAS, 2003-09-01; DVD (Box 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Teamsters Rally- Coney Island Tape 2 CINTAS, 2003-09-01; DVD (Box 1)
  - IBT- MPLS Rally Tape 02, 2001-02-17; DVD (Box 1)
- Conferences, Conventions and Meetings, Series 4
  - 17th Conference of Teamsters (9 Minutes), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Central Conference Committee (8 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 2001 Convention Video: Opening, Building Better Lives Through Organizing, Political Action, and Strong Contracts (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - "Teamsters" (English) Canadian Conference of Teamsters, ND (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 1: Music, Intro with Claude Brown, Ron Carey, 1997 (Box 3, Item 15)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 2, 1997 (Box 3, Item 16)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 3, 1997 (Box 3, Item 17)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 4, 1997 (Box 3, Item 18)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 5, 1997 (Box 3, Item 19)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 6, 1997 (Box 3, Item 20)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 7, 1997 (Box 3, Item 21)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 8, 1997 (Box 3, Item 22)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 9, 1997 (Box 3, Item 23)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 10, 1997 (Box 3, Item 24)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 11, 1997 (Box 3, Item 25)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 12: Delores Huerta / Mary Mendez Apple Organizing Campaign, 1997 (Box 3, Item 26)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 13, 1997 (Box 3, Item 27)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 14, 1997 (Box 3, Item 28)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 15, 1997 (Box 3, Item 29)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 16, 1997 (Box 3, Item 30)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Convention Las Vegas, NV, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Congress Speaks at the 19th Convention of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Senator Eugene McCarthy (D-MN), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 17th Convention Southern Conference- IBT (17 Minutes), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - IBT 2001 Convention Close (10 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Teamsters Endorse Gore unity Conference- Las Vegas (35 Minutes), 2000; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - 26th International Convention Opening Video, 2001; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Congress Speaks at the 19th Convention IBT (36 minutes), ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 1, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 2, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 3, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 4, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 5, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - IBT Legislative Conference San Francisco Reel 8 Nauve Miller, Tony Gamino, Barbara George, Local 601, Rank & File ENG on way leaflet Lucky, Interviews on Bus, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - IBT Legislative Conference San Francisco Reel 11 Discussion on Striker Replacement, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - IBT Legislative Conference San Francisco Reel 12 Jim Hightower, Populist Spokesperson, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - IBT Legislative Conference San Francisco Reel 12A Jim Hightower Speech- continued, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - IBT Legislative Conference San Francisco Reel 13 Fair Trade Agreement Continued Q & A, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - IBT Legislative Conference San Francisco Reel 14 Tim Scully, Mario Paruchi, Dave Sweeny Discussion- Deregulation, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - IBT Legislative Conference San Francisco Reel 15 Discussion- Deregulation continued Tim Scully, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 1, 1997-09-19; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 128)